[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube
channel Marine World. Friends, in today's
video, I will provide you with detailed information about the ICC
Lombard Health Insurance Policy.
Friends,
before continuing in the video, I
would like to request you that if you have
n't yet subscribed to this channel,
please do subscribe. And if you
like the video, please share it. So
friends, let's start the video with this.
Friends,
ICC Lombard General Insurance Company, located in India, is one of the
top private sector insurance companies.
It is a subsidiary of ICC Bank
Limited and Fairfax Financial Holdings
Limited, Canada.
Friends, ICC Lombard General
Insurance Company has been
offering a variety of innovative products to customers for
years, depending on their needs. Friends, ICC
Lombard General Insurance Company
offers insurance products in different areas,
such as two-wheeler,
health, and travel
insurance products. This
means that customers have seen this insurance product.
Friends, the insurance product
offered by ICC Lombard General Insurance Company is
comprehensive.  Along with coverage, it is also
known for providing quality services. In this video, we will learn in detail about the ICC
Lombard Health Insurance plan,
such as what are the benefits of this plan,
how much coverage is provided by this plan, and what are the eligibility criteria for purchasing
ICC Lombard Health Insurance.
We will learn about all these in detail in today's video,
so friends,
please watch this video till the end. Friends, let me
tell you in detail about what are the benefits of ICC Lombard Health Insurance policy.
Friends, currently the
cost of medical expenses on health has increased a lot
and it is likely to increase further in the future.
Friends, you can take ICC Lombard Health
Insurance policy to financially secure yourself and your family
during a medical emergency. That is,
you
can provide financial security to your family.
Friends, if
you are a salaried person, then you are given a
health insurance policy by your employer,
but by taking this policy
you are guaranteed only till you  You work with your
employer.
Furthermore, your family members
cannot be included in the policy. With the
ICC Lombard Health Insurance policy,
you can provide health insurance benefits to yourself and additional family members. Due to the
current lifestyle,
many diseases are occurring
among the younger generation, which is why family
health insurance is essential.
For lifestyle-related illnesses,
ICC Lombard Health Insurance
offers plans with high coverage at a low cost.
Compared to individual health
insurance policies, you
can save on free insurance. When a
health insurance policy covers more than one
person, the coverage is increased by the
ICC Lombard Health Insurance Company.
ICC Lombard Health
Insurance applies insurance based on your family's needs.
It helps you select
a better health insurance
policy, keeping in mind all your family's needs.
Friends, in ICC Lombard Health
Insurance, you are also provided tax benefit under Section
80D of Income Tax Act on the premium paid by the person. In
this way, you
can increase your tax savings through the policy.
Friends, Section 19 has also been made available through ICC Lombard Health Insurance
Policy.
Under this, if an
individual is admitted in the hospital, then
his expenses are borne by ICC Lombard Health
Insurance.
Friends, while claiming the
insurance amount, the person has to
bear some extra fee himself,
but through ICC Lombard Health
Insurance Policy, you do
not have to face any kind of problem. Friends,
this company makes KP on the
insurance amount in its health insurance policy,
but through ICC
Lombard Health Insurance Policy, no
kind of compensation is made.
You are provided coverage up to the limit as per the needs of your family.
Friends, if
you are admitted in the hospital for more than 24 hours due to medical treatment, then the
medical expenses incurred during that time, hospital room
rent etc. are also covered.  Doctor's bills and medicine bills are also covered under this policy.
ICC Lombard Health Insurance also offers benefits for medical expenses incurred
30 days before
and 60 days after hospitalization. ICC Lombard Health Insurance
also provides benefits for day-care treatment.
If you are admitted to a hospital for
less than 24 hours,
you receive the benefit of day-care treatment.
ICC
Lombard Health Insurance
also covers expenses incurred under this policy.
ICC Lombard Health Insurance offers
wellness points for various business and fitness activities, which
you can use for consultations with doctors, payment of medicines,
etc.
If the duration of the health insurance policy is
free, you receive a
bonus in the superannuation. It provides up
to 50% more insurance amount than the insurance amount.
ICC Lombard
Health Insurance also covers ambulance expenses in case of an emergency.  The policyholder
provides a health check-up coupon with every policy. This coupon allows
you to easily get your health checked,
free of charge. The
ICC Lombard Health Insurance policy
also covers ambulance expenses.
Under ICC Lombard Health Insurance, you can avail
of this policy anywhere in the world.
If you undergo
treatment abroad, the expenses incurred are covered. The
ICC Lombard Health Insurance
policy also provides coverage for organ donor expenses.
This
policy also offers a reset benefit.
If you
feel the insurance amount is
insufficient for your family's needs, you
can reset your Lombard Health Insurance policy at any time.
Under the ICC Lombard Health Insurance policy, when you are admitted to a cashless hospital, the
insurance amount is
directly paid to the hospital bill.
You don't need to wait for this.
Some people are covered with immediate effect,
whereas
for some people there is a waiting period of up to two years.
Friends, in ICC Lombard
Health Insurance Policy, you are given a
free look period of 15 years. So,
if you feel that
you are not satisfied with this policy, then you can terminate
your policy anytime within 15 years.
Friends, now I will
tell you in detail about the eligibility for ICC Lombard Health Insurance Policy.
Friends, to buy
ICC Lombard Health Insurance Policy for yourself and your family members, you should be
18 years of age or above.
Friends, to cover children under ICC Lombard Health Insurance
's family insurance policy, their age should be
three
to three months or more.
Friends, to buy individual health
insurance policy for children, their age should be
6 years or more. Before buying
ICC Lombard Health Insurance Policy for a person aged 46 years or above, get a test done
at designated diagnostic centers.
Only after passing the medical test, they can be given such Lombard
Health Insurance policies.
So friends, in today's video we learned
what is Lombard Health Insurance Policy and about it, I have
told you in detail in today's video.
Friends, if you liked this video, then do
share it with your friends
and if you are new to the channel, then do
subscribe to it. We will meet
in the next video with some other topic. Till then,
thank you.